<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>\n<rss version="2.0">\n    <channel>\n        <title>GOV - NSW</title>\n        <link>https://suppliers.buy.nsw.gov.au/</link>\n        <description>NSW Gov Tech</description>\n        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:15:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>\n        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>\n        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>\n        <language>en</language>\n        <image>\n            <title>GOV - NSW</title>\n            <url>https://example.com/image.png</url>\n            <link>https://suppliers.buy.nsw.gov.au/</link>\n        </image>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[NBLHD CTG Foetal Monitoring System]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=01555628-9E6E-46DE-170E93FB638AA7E8</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=01555628-9E6E-46DE-170E93FB638AA7E8</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[NBLHD CTG Foetal Monitoring System]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[Global Mapper Software Licenses, Maintenance and Support]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=0D5988F5-A0AF-BBA6-9B38B85CDDF2D732</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=0D5988F5-A0AF-BBA6-9B38B85CDDF2D732</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[Spatial Services currently holds 12 BlueMarble Global Mapper Standard Network Licenses + maintenance and 3 BlueMarble Global Mapper Pro v25 Network Licenses with associated maintenance.\nOnly suppliers listed under the ICT Services Scheme for Category M09 are eligible to apply.]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[Bundle 29 Workshop ICT Panel]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=96ABCAD6-D39C-BAA3-626EA9B145BF5E7A</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=96ABCAD6-D39C-BAA3-626EA9B145BF5E7A</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[The Advanced Manufacturing Research Facility (AMRF) will be Australia s first industry-focused manufacturing development facility with a singular mission to accelerate the adoption of advanced technology in manufacturing. Key to a facility of this style and magnitude are the supporting items required to maintain safe and productive working habits. These items will constitute a large range of categories, and the WPCA is actively seeking expressions of interests from suppliers interested in being evaluated for inclusion on a Workshop ICT Procurement Panel for the AMRF.\nThe attached Invitation To Respond (ITR) documents describe the services required and set out the conditions of tendering. The ITR will remain open for submissions for the duration of the contract until 30 June 2026. Any submissions received will be evaluated every quarter starting July 2024, September 2024, December 2024 then March 2025, June 2025, September 2025, December 2025 and March 2026, June 2026. To be included in the first batch of evaluations, your proposal must be lodged prior to Wednesday 31st July 2024 at 5:00pm AEST. \nYou should note that Western Parkland City Authority may issue an addendum to the invitation documents prior to the close of the ITR.\nIt is your firm s responsibility to ensure that it submits and lodges a compliant ITR response. Should you require any clarification on any aspect of the invitation documents or tender process, you should contact Western Parkland City Authority Procurement at amrfpanels@wpca.sydney We are unable due to issues of probity to discuss these issues with you verbally.\nConfidentiality: You should note that any individual(s) proposed as a resource in you firm s proposal must complete and sign the Confidentiality Deed Poll (provided as a Word document) and this duly executed document must be lodged as part of your submission.\nCode of Ethics and Conduct: A copy of the Authority s Code of Ethics and Conduct for Procurement activities is included as part of the ITR documents. It is a contractual responsibility placed on all Suppliers to provide a copy of this document to any individual engaged in delivering the Services. A central issue in the Authority s code of conduct is the mitigation of any actual, perceived, or potential conflict of interests which may arise when a person engaged in delivering the Services is confronted with issues that that cause a conflict between that person s public duties and their personal or private interests. It is incumbent upon any individual engaged on any Western Parkland City Authority contract to disclose to the Authority any conflicts of interest as soon as practicable after the situation reasonably comes to their attention. Any and all such conflicts of interests must be advised to Western Parkland City Authority (amrfpanels@wpca.sydney)\nWestern Parkland City Authority looks forward to reviewing your firm s proposal.\nAn online briefing will be held via MS Teams on the week starting 15th July 2024. Please email the amrfpanels@wpca.sydney email address with your Company Name, Contact Person, Contact Email Address before Tuesday 9th July 2024 and we will send you a link to the briefing.]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[RAA Loan Solution]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=D0D314B9-9F65-22C5-E310ED31C6A4B6DB</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=D0D314B9-9F65-22C5-E310ED31C6A4B6DB</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[The Rural Assistance Authority (RAA) is issuing a Request for Tender (RFT) for the procurement and implementation of an off-the-shelf Loan Management Solution. This solution aims to enhance process efficiency, compliance, transparency, and customer experience while aligning with industry standards.]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[RFT for telecom expense management and mobile fleet management services contract]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=D491AD87-D77D-49E5-CED23215EB4BBE40</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=D491AD87-D77D-49E5-CED23215EB4BBE40</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[Mobile fixed network expense management services for Department of Customer Service and GovConnect\n(up to 24 months contract term)]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[Transport for NSW Opal Ticketing Retail Solution – Invitation for Market Sounding]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=358423DC-9F2A-2B64-58C2ED52897E8E8F</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=358423DC-9F2A-2B64-58C2ED52897E8E8F</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[Transport for NSW (TfNSW) seeks to engage with industry to inform and shape its strategy for the Opal Ticketing Retail Solution for the NSW transport network.]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[Drone Operational Equipment / Software]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=C54375D8-B65E-24BC-49D94BC6EC6202AB</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=C54375D8-B65E-24BC-49D94BC6EC6202AB</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[TfNSW seeks expressions of interest for solutions of\nVTOL/Fixed Wing drones, DiaB solutions and AI software]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[Domain-based Messaging, Authentication, Reporting and Conformance (DMARC) reporting tool for all of NSW Government]]></title>\n            <link>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=FDEB58D1-C999-CBB4-D05670955313C7F7</link>\n            <guid>https://www.tenders.nsw.gov.au/wsroc/?event=public.rft.show&amp;RFTUUID=FDEB58D1-C999-CBB4-D05670955313C7F7</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[In 2021, Cyber Security commenced the DMARC project, rolling out DMARC across 11 portfolios, 180 agencies and state organisations, eight state-owned corporations and 128 NSW local councils, protecting more than 21,000 NSW Government domains.\nThe core objective of this tender is to engage a provider that can provide a DMARC reporting platform to preventthreat actors from abusing NSW Government domains while providing insight into the traffic against these domains through a threat reporting mechanism, and related account management services to Cyber Security NSW]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[Operational Telecommunications Equipment, Infrastructure and Services (ITS2573)]]></title>\n            <link>/scheme/2F4D6FCB-A284-8C44-137434F7292ED668</link>\n            <guid>/scheme/2F4D6FCB-A284-8C44-137434F7292ED668</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[SCM0053 is for provision of a range of equipment, infrastructure, and specialist services to build, operate, and maintain telecommunication networks.]]></description>\n        </item>\n        <item>\n            <title><![CDATA[Prequalification Scheme: ICT Services]]></title>\n            <link>/scheme/6B1F91AE-B3CC-0F0E-17267D5EF7BCEB9E</link>\n            <guid>/scheme/6B1F91AE-B3CC-0F0E-17267D5EF7BCEB9E</guid>\n            <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>\n            <description><![CDATA[The ICT Services Scheme is mandated for all suppliers who deliver ICT goods and services to the NSW Government.]]></description>\n        </item>\n    </channel>\n</rss>